realtyminister.com 2013-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Realty Minister

Realtyminister.com is an online property portal endeavoring constantly to provide you with premium property services. Since we are strongly committed to your right to privacy, we have drawn out a privacy statement with regard to the information we collect from you.

By providing your personal details to us, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to this statement, please do not provide your personal details to us. This privacy statement is incorporated into, and part of, the Terms and Conditions, which govern your use of the site in general.

We may need to update this privacy statement from time to time. We recommend that you regularly check this page to ensure that you have read the most recent version.

This Privacy Policy describes how we handle your personal information for our services on the realtyminister.com website. By accepting the Privacy Policy and the User Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective on 01/01/2012.

**What information you need to give in to use this site?** ** **

You can browse our sites without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers located in the United States or anywhere else around the world. We gather information from members and guests who apply for the various services our site offers. We also collect additional information about your property. We may collect and store the following personal information but may not be limited to: email address, physical contact information, and financial information, such as credit card or bank account numbers; transactional information based on your activities on the sites (such as your purchase history); billing and other information you provide to purchase and dispatch an invoice; correspondence through our sites, and correspondence sent to us; other information from your interaction with our sites, services, content and advertising, including computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, ad data, IP address and standard web log information; additional information we ask you to submit to authenticate yourself or if we believe you are violating site policies (for example, we may ask you to send us an ID or bill to verify your address, or to answer additional questions online to help verify your identity or ownership of an item you list); information from other companies, such as demographic and navigation data.

**How the site uses the information it collects / tracks?** ** **

Realtyminister.com collects information from our clients primarily to ensure that we are able to fulfill your requirements and to deliver personalized experience. We don’t sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our services, content and advertising. If you don’t wish to receive marketing communications from us or participate in our ad-customization programs, simply indicate your preference in your user account on realtyminister.com or by following the directions provided with the communication or advertisement.

**With whom the site shares the information we collects/tracks?** ** **

The information collected from any of our clients is shared with their approval to individuals and organizations. Realtyminister.com does not sell, rent, or loan any identifiable information at the individual level regarding its customers to any third party. Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and security and revealed unless you want it to. We are also bound to cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer.

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to: provide the services and customer support you request; resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement; customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising; tell you about our services, targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences; and compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties.

**Where and whom your information is disclosed?** ** **

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.  
We may also share your personal information with: Service providers under contract who help with our business operations (such as fraud investigations, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs and co-branded credit cards).

  * Other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service).
  * Law enforcement or other governmental officials, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity. In such events, we will disclose information relevant to the investigation, such as name, city, state, zip code, telephone number, email address, User ID history, IP address, fraud complaints, and bidding and listing history.
  * Other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity. (Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. If your personal information will be used contrary to this policy, you will receive prior notice.)

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

**What is the function of cookies?**

In common with many websites, we use “cookies” to help us gather the following information from visitors to toptable.co.uk, for example: the IP address from which you access the site the type of browser and operating system used to access the site the date and time of your access to the site the pages you visit the internet address of the website from which you accessed the site A cookie is a small data file that our server sends to your browser when you visit the site. The use of cookies helps us to assist your use of certain aspects of the site. You can delete cookies at any time or you can set your browser to reject or disable cookies. If you do disable cookies some functions on the site may not work correctly.  
We use information from cookies, for example, to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the type of technology that our visitors use. Cookies help us to monitor what sort of content is popular and to assess visitors browsing habits. When a user revisits the site, we may recognize the user by the cookie and customize the user’s experience accordingly. We can use this information to continually improve the content and usability of the site.  
We may compile and report to third parties (such as advertisers) aggregate statistics about our users in terms of numbers, traffic patterns and related site information.  
We do not connect the information collected through cookies with other information that is personally identifiable, unless required or permitted to do so by law or to enforce the Terms & Conditions.

**How the information of your account is protected?** ** **

Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your Realtyminister password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify Realtyminister and change your password.

**What do we mean by Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information?**

You can see, review and change most of your personal information by signing on to your Realtyminister user account. Generally, we will not manually modify your personal information because it is very difficult to verify your identity remotely. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate. Upon your request, we will close your account and remove your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Realtyminister User Agreement, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

**What has been done for your security?**

Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the site. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**What do we mean by Third Parties?**

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether vendors or users on our sites or other sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Realtyminister does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.
